{
    "subject": "Karl_Hartl",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Mozart__1955_film_",
    "human_readable": "Karl Hartl directed the 1955 film about Mozart.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9623935222625732,
            "question": "Who directed the 1955 film about Mozart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534615278244019,
            "question": "Was a film made about Mozart in 1955?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9044265747070312,
            "question": "What year did Karl Hartl direct a film about Mozart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8923125267028809,
            "question": "What type of film was made about Mozart in 1955?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7894889116287231,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Karl Hartl."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.781485378742218,
            "question": "Is Karl Hartl known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7005460262298584,
            "question": "What year was the film about Mozart released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6554492712020874,
            "question": "What subject was the 1955 film about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6401864290237427,
            "question": "Who is the subject of the 1955 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6075286865234375,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made the Mozart film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Hartl directed the 1955 film about Mozart.",
            "html": "yago_14723_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the subject of the 1955 film?",
            "html": "yago_14723_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What subject was the 1955 film about?",
            "html": "yago_14723_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film about Mozart released?",
            "html": "yago_14723_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14723_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Karl Hartl directed the 1955 Austrian drama film \"Mozart\" (also known as \"The Life and Loves of Mozart\"). Therefore, the query \"Karl Hartl directed the 1955 film about Mozart\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}